You were on Tucker Carlson just a few
days ago, Clayton. I've been on a couple
of times. I think I'm going to go back
on in the next four or five weeks. I
like Tucker very much. I consider him to
be a friend, and I have to tell you, I'm
genuinely worried for his safety.
Tucker is one of those rare
truth-tellers.
He He speaks whatever happens to be on
his mind, but it's always very well
thought out. He's not afraid to call
important people on the carpet for
things that they've said or done.
In the current political climate, in the
post Let's call it the post-Charlie Kirk
era.
Do you think Tucker Carlson has reason
to be worried?
>> I think he He wouldn't admit that.
You know, he doesn't like to He never
likes to have the focus be on him at
all.
I've known him for years, and he's he's
never like me, me, me, like
navel-gazing. He hates that. He hates
that with a passion, you know.
Um
Oh, I need a, you know, large security
contingent cuz I'm so important. Like,
he's not that kind of person at all.
Um
But look, the SBU tried to to to kill
blew up his almost blew up his car when
he went to Moscow. Like Like, there's
some realities here. You have these nut
job, you know, you know, MAGA
influencers, these sort of pro-Israel
Zionists who are at basically actively
calling for him to be arrested,
attacked. Um and they have platforms. I
mean, they're literally not thrown off
of X. They're calling for like the
arrest and hurting of his family, and
they're still somehow on X, and they
still have jobs at like Fox News
somehow. Like, when I worked at Fox
News, if I would have called for like
the death of a human being,
like, I would have been fired. But this
is a new era, so you can call for, you
know, attacks on certain people like
that. Um
So, yeah, and I think, you know, he's
he's doing what he needs to do to
protect himself, and I'm sure he's got a
wife, you know, his his wife is probably
wanting to make sure he's safe and
protected, and he's got smarter He's got
people around him who are saying, "Hey,
Tucker, I know you don't like this to be
about yourself, but we're going to
protect you." So, um yeah, but I don't
want to
speak out of turn for what's going on
behind the scenes, but yeah, he is a
truth-teller, and of course that's a
small um that's a
>> [clears throat]
>> that's a commodity these days. It's hard
to find those.
>> Why is it that there are so few people,
whether they're on the political left or
the political right in the United
States, who are unwilling to tell the
truth about the situation on the ground
in Israel and Palestine? And and more
specifically, what I mean is
that
Tucker had, for example, Mother Agafia,
uh George Stephanopoulos' sister, who's
a Greek Orthodox nun. Uh she has lived
in
in the West Bank or in East Jerusalem
for decades, and she gave a very long
She had a very long conversation with
Tucker about what life is like for
Christians
in Israel. It's extremely difficult.
Uh Tucker then went to Israel
and interviewed
Ambassador Mike Huckabee.
In my estimation, that interview was a
disaster, an unmitigated disaster for
Huckabee.
He was unable to answer Tucker's
questions. And when he did answer
Tucker's questions, he essentially
turned the entire Middle East against
the United States saying that
God promised Israel to the Jews.
Israel means everything from the
Euphrates River to the Nile, which is
essentially the entire Middle East, and
they can go ahead and take it, he said.
He didn't care. So, first of all, how
much damage do you think that does? But
secondly, and I want to ask both of you
your opinions. But secondly, um
why is this the prevailing position
among American Christians when it was
Palestinian Christians who were the
original Christians
and they get no love from American
Christians.
>> Yeah, this is something that I've been
pretty obsessed with in the last 2 years
because I, you know, I was inspired by
the rise of Christianity, the popularity
of Christianity around the Trump
election because it seemed like there
were some conservative values that were
revalidated in the election of Donald
Trump. And I thought what that meant was
sort of family values,
um you know,
sort of
I don't know, a refutation of some of
the sexual perversions that was so
popular during the Biden years.
And then for this group to turn around
and support a genocide and support a
terrorist government, I was confused by.
And so
I I went back to where this began. I
recently finished the the Canfield book
called uh Scofield and his amazing book
or something like that. Um it's a tough
read, but it tells the story of the
Scofield Bible, which is the informant
text of evangelicals. And I thought,
why? Why why do they do this? Where did
it come from? It turns out that Cyrus
Scofield himself was a bit of a
scoundrel. He was a Confederate war
soldier. He was the district attorney in
Kansas. He had lied about his
Confederate uh service to the army. He
defected from there as well. He says
he's from Tennessee, he's not, he's from
Michigan. He had two daughters and a
Catholic wife who he left penniless even
though he became quite rich. And then uh
before he did that, he was sued several
times for fraud.
Um he he just was a scoundrel and then
all of a sudden Christian conversion and
he's a star, a rising star in the
Christian movement. This is around early
1900s.
He moves to Massachusetts. He becomes a
part of this Niagara Falls Convention.
And at the in the late 1800s, there was
this appetite for end-of-the-world
theology because the world was hard back
then. And he joins this movement and
somehow becomes a member of the Lotus
Club in New York City. The Lotus Club is
a club of Wall Street bankers and early
Zionists. They're the ones who fund the
Scofield Bible. They see in him the
snake oil salesman they need. They fund
this movement and then this nobody, this
guy who'd been a scoundrel his whole
life, is now this popular theologian,
popular priest,
uh bishop,
religious leader
who never had and and all of a sudden
this book is just everywhere. Why? How
did that happen? Well, do evangelicals
know that it's Wall Street backed? That
it was the brainchild of Wall Street and
early Zionist? I don't think they do.
And so their allegiance to this comes
from a pretty rotten place and I don't
think they know it.
>> Well, there are evangelicals that we
know that have broken free of this and
had educated themselves on this and
that's why they want to suppress this
story because if more evangelicals learn
about this, if you go to Texas for
instance and you know, to go to any of
those churches and you were to educate
them on this, they would they would cast
you out. So they don't want you to know
that this entire line of Christianity
has, you know, been co-opted by like a
scoundrel and a
>> And Scofield's original churches were in
Dallas. So, you know, that was born of
that movement and and then it just grew.
It was it was Texas and then
the Northeast.
>> But we have friends who broken out of
this, you know, educated themselves and
once they realize like that this whole
the their you know, their whole movement
has been is a canard in many ways backed
by this scoundrel and like this fake
version of the Bible in many ways backed
by Wall Street Zionists, they're like
outraged by it and they become
non-denominational.
They're kind of they're kind of
wandering around the desert like looking
for a new church because they were just
they can't believe that their whole 20
30 years of being raised in that
environment was a was a lie.
>> lies.
>> You know, I for years I was a I was an
adjunct professor of intelligence
studies at Liberty University in
Lynchburg, Virginia, which is the
largest evangelical university in the
world. And when they first approached me
with this job offer, I said I said, "Are
you sure you want me? You and I probably
disagree on 95% of the issues. Why would
you want me to be a professor?" And
without missing a beat, the dean the
dean of the Jesse Helms School of
Government said, "Um
because torture's not Christian." And I
said, "You know what? I'll take the
job."
And so I really really enjoyed my time
at Liberty, but we clashed constantly
over this issue of Middle Eastern
Christians. I just I I would take them
to task every single time I would hear
them say something about sending a
delegation to convert people to
Christianity uh in Palestine. And I
said, "Th- This is where Christianity
began. You guys are snuffing out
Palestinian Christians." There was one
student that I had
who told me that she was going on a
mission. And I said, "Oh, that's great.
What are you going to do?" "Well, I'm
going to I'm going to bring people to
Christ." I said, "Cool, where are you
going?" And she said, "Um Macedonia." I
said, "But they're already Christians in
Macedonia.
They're they're Orthodox like me."
>> Well, look at Iran. What's the plan for
Iran?
>> don't consider it their type of
Christian. It's almost as if they're
savage type like Yes, but we really
understand it and they don't. And so we
are going to
I'm sorry I interrupted you, but let me
just finish this point. Their theology
is fundamentally conflicting because
evangelicals want eventually for all the
Jews that they support to convert to
Christianity. The Jews absolutely do not
want that. They want this war to bring
about the coming of their Messiah and
they will remain Jews. So, they have two
very different end goals. They're just
kind of, you know, merged right now on
the war and what it will affect. And
it's like, "Let's not talk about what
happens after the rapture." I think
you're coming to me, you think you're
going to you. We'll just run along.
Let's just have a little war.
>> rapture being a late 19th century
American evangelical invention, by the
way.
>> Yes. Yes, again coming out of this
Niagara Falls
uh if you study the late 1800s movement
and, you know, out of that was born
Jehovah's Witnesses, which I was raised
one. And yes, and evangelicals and this
like end of times type theology, which I
don't think you understand how much
power that hands the government. I'm
sorry, go ahead.
>> No, I was just going to say the savages
thing is really important. Like this
idea that if you're at a Dallas like
megachurch, that you're somehow more
civilized than these Christians who've
grown up in the Holy Land. Um also,
what's going to happen to the nearly 1
million Christians that live in Iran?
>> That's right.
>> I are we
are we in any way discerning when we're
carpet bombing Tehran how many of tho-
those we're kill- killing? And how many
Christian churches are throughout Iran,
by the way? I mean, I don't know the
number. Maybe you have a better number
on it, but there are many many and a
nearly I think a million Christians that
live in Iran. So, I'm sure we'll
prioritize them.
>> Many of the churches go back more than a
thousand years.
The There's a long history of
Christianity in Iran. That's just
ignored. It's just ignored today.
You know,
>> I'm just so struck I just we
we're not allowed to talk about the
Christians being killed in Syria. We're
not allowed to talk about the Christians
being killed in Gaza. For some reason,
if you bring it up, then you're an
anti-Semite, which I just can't wrap my
head around that that that that
reasoning. Like you're we're not allowed
to talk about your carpet bombing of
Gaza is killing a lot of Christians or
displacing a lot of Christians or, you
know, what's happening in Syria. We
can't talk about that. The beheading of
Christians. We you do it. anti-Semite if
you bring that up, and it's infuriating.
>> I have to tell you a a little story, and
it's it's apropos of of Syria and the
situation in Syria, but it's it's not
going to sound like it. So,
when my two eldest sons were little,
they loved wrestling, fake wrestling,
right? Uh World Wrestling Entertainment
wrestling. And so, I splurged one uh one
weekend, and I bought us tickets to see
wrestling at Madison Square Garden. So,
we go, and we're watching these guys
smash chairs over each others' heads,
and jump and land on tables and smash
the table. And I said to my eldest son,
who I mean, now he's 33, but at the time
he was
I guess nine or eight eight years old. I
said, "Buddy, I don't get it. Which one
is the good guy?"
And he said, "That's [laughter] just it,
Dad. There is no good guy."
That was the situation in Syria.
>> Mhm.
>> It's possible [clears throat]
to just have a situation where there is
no good guy. And so, what you do is you
support the least bad guy.
Uh
Bashar al-Assad had a lot of problems,
right?
He was a a dictator. He was the son of a
dictator. He used a heavy hand against
his own people. But, he was the only
thing standing between the Christian
community of Syria and complete
annihilation.
And so, we decided we didn't like his
politics, and we worked with the
Israelis and the Turks to throw him out.
And now he's in exile.
So, who takes over Syria, but the former
deputy leader of ISIS,
who apparently was chosen by the CIA,
leads me to believe he was probably a
CIA
paid CIA agent, but that's we can talk
about that at some other point. Um
and there's a genocide against
Christians.
So, why the short-sighted policies
coming out of the United States? If if
we're supposed to be so Christian, so
pro-Christian, we talk about
Judeo-Christian values, and then we
support the wholesale slaughter of the
world's original Christians.
I'm just not understanding, you know,
where the disconnect comes from.
When we come back, we will have more
with the hosts of Redacted. I'm John
Kiriakou, and this is The Deep State.
Stay right there.
We're joined back again today by our
guests, Natalie and Clayton Morris.
They're the hosts of the hit show
Redacted.
There's a video that's that's going
around on TikTok and other platforms
right now.
Uh it's a a young woman who's an
American Evangelical Christian,
and she goes to Israel for the very
first time, and she starts saying things
like, you know, "Israel! Israel!" And a
group of young Jewish boys walks up to
her, and they spit right on her. Spit
right in her face. And she wipes it off,
and she says, "Holy spit. Israel's spit.
It's holy. It's okay." And then she she
goes into the um Old City,
and um
she's got a microphone, and she's trying
to interview people about, you know,
"Isn't Israel great?" Over to you. And
a a teenager takes a a backpack and just
smashes her in the head with the
backpack.
And she starts crying. She's like, "Why
are they doing this to me? I love
Israel. Why? Why are they doing this?"
It's like, "Lady, don't you get it? They
don't care about you.
They only care about them."
There's no room for you in Israel.
>> It's like a form of Stockholm Syndrome,
in a way.
>> That's exactly what it is.
>> it's
Like, you can just continue to beat us
down, and we're just going to continue
to kiss your ass. We'll continue to do
your bidding. You can send your prime
minister to
uh to Washington D.C. for the seventh
time.
We'll take your money. We'll do all do
everything. You You can buy our American
businesses. You can take over TikTok.
We'll hand that to you. And then when we
go there and you'll treat us like
garbage, but it's okay. You're allowed
to treat us like garbage. That's fine.
Just keep treating us like garbage and
we'll just continue to take it. At some
point, someone's going to snap.
>> Yeah. Yeah, that's right. You know, I
[snorts] I have to ask you about that,
too.
Um about about sort of
taking over.
Why is it, do you think,
that a country as small as Israel
is able to exert such
outsized influence, not just in
politics. We've had that conversation a
thousand times. Not just in American
politics, but in American business, in
entertainment, in banking, even even in
the defense industries. You know,
we we either give or sell Israel
anything it wants, anything at all. And
the Israelis have very close and abiding
relations with most of the major
American defense contractors.
Why?
>> I mean, this is something that's plagued
me and I've You know, if you go back and
read John Mearsheimer's The Israel
Lobby.
>> Yes.
>> And you at least try to understand how
over decades this grew and grew and grew
and there were politicians like John F.
Kennedy, for instance, who
um certainly didn't want this and were
kind of openly against it. They wind up
dead, of course. So, I think there is
I I don't know. I think the money I
mean, follow the money at the heart of
it, right? Follow the money and the
influence inside of Washington and
realize that almost every politician in
Washington to Thomas Massie's credit,
when he admitted that everyone has like
an AIPAC handler,
um someone who funnels money to them,
make sure that they're on message. And
then when you realize then that the
defense industry has
uh factories manufacturing. One thing I
learned years ago and I think it's grown
tremendously since I learned it, but the
idea that
a lot of the defense manufacturing sits
in the backyard. They've they've very
strategically built
little weapons parts factories in
different parts of the country. So,
Boeing doesn't just have their main
Boeing operation center, but they have
like, you know, this little piece that's
built over here and they build it in the
back of So, they've they've spread
themselves all across the United States
so that they're essentially in the
backyards of almost every politician.
>> That's right.
>> So, that every politician can say, you
know, Boeing's in my backyard. I've got
to protect them. It it it benefits the
weapons industry, but it's also
represents my district. Well, how many
districts? Because they've spread
themselves Honeywell, Northrop Grumman,
all of these like little divisions all
across the United States.
So, that's one big piece of it.
And then every member of Congress takes
money and influence and works with
AIPAC. So, the money flows in and it
flows right back out and it's all one
big money laundering operation and
they're all benefiting from it and there
are very few who aren't benefiting from
it. And if they aren't, then they're
they're cast out. I mean, people like
Marjorie Taylor Greene or, you know,
Matt Gaetz or Congressman Thomas Massie.
Look look the hell that he's going
through right now being, you know,
trying to be primary. Um so, I think
it's it's a massive money laundering
operation at the heart of it. That's
That's how I see it and it just flows
back. So, just follow the money, follow
the weapons.
>> And and I have to say I also think
>> I'm sorry. Go ahead. Go ahead, Natalie.
No, no, no, please.
>> No, no, you go ahead.
>> I was going to say I I learned recently
that it's even deeper than just that. Um
I have a friend who got a call from a
Texas state senator.
And he said, "Hey, we'd like to do
um a a resolution, a state senate
resolution naming
such and such a date as John Smith Day."
Uh he said, "It's pro forma. We do about
140 of these a year where you're going
to get a proclamation with the big seal
of Texas and the governor's signature,
and it's going to be, you know, your
day." He said, "Oh, great. Okay."
So, a couple of weeks pass, and the
state senator calls back, and he says,
"Listen, that uh John Smith Day, that's
not going to happen."
And he said, "Why? You said it was pro
forma."
And the state senator said,
"The AIPAC lobbyists objected to it."
And I said, "Wait a minute. They have
AIPAC lobbyists in the state capitals?
For for the state legislatures?" And he
said, "Not just in the state capitals.
They have lobbyists
all over America. They're lobbying in
local city council elections. Maybe
you're running for the water board of
whatever city or the garbage commission
of whatever city you happen to be living
in,
and there are AIPAC lobbyists even at
that level."
>> Yeah.
>> That's unbelievable. I'm not surprised
though, at all. I mean,
you know, you can see That's where real
politics is born, right at the local
level, at the school board level, um
you know, in your in your mayoral races.
That's That's the influence. That's how,
for instance, we're in the state of
Colorado, like everyone should read how
the state of Colorado went from being a
red state to a blue state. And it was
all done specifically at the local
level, and with the ad spend, the
targeted ad spend in these specific
races. And now, you know, Colorado is is
by all accounts a blue state. On
election night, it immediately, as soon
as they called it, "Hey, Colorado polls
are closed." They immediately called it
for
Kamala Harris. You know, it's
unbelievable. In a in a landslide
election for Trump, Colorado went blue,
but it all happened at the local
elections.
>> Yeah.
You know, when you study If I were to
If I were to submit a term paper about
this, the hypothesis would be that the
sort of communist Zionist infiltration
of the US government happened very
early. When you study the movement that
became McCarthyism, McCarthy was right.
There were Soviet communist spies
working inside the State Department. He
did not make that up. He got that from a
State Department report that you cannot
find on national archives, and he was
excoriated from it, even though the FBI
had corroborating files. Hoover hung him
out to dry. Hoover himself had been
taking this to the White House, and it
had been ignored. Why? Why this this
communist infiltration? And then you
look at There's a book called The Iron
Curtain Over America by John Beaty, who
was a State Department
ex-
representative. He worked for the State
Department, and he was warning that a
lot of these communists in the '50s
and who also were Zionists
were converting to Judaism in order to
make this claim that related to Zionism.
And he said he compared it to someone
converting to a Native American religion
and saying that gives me claim to the
United States. It It doesn't, right? And
so it has And so if I were, again, like
I would need a little bit more time to
flush out this term paper, but I think
that I can trace it through early early
American politics, and it's a long game.